Dean Zadok

Graduated recently from the Technion's CS department, with 2 years of experience in developing machine learning applications in several platforms. Have very strong skills in taking ideas from scratch and apply them, with auto-dictation capabilities and a great work ethic.

danielxp75@gmail.com github.com/deanzadok linkedin.com/in/dean-za dok-36886791

ACADEMIC PUBLICATIONS

Explorations and Lessons Learned in Building an Autonomous Formula SAE Car from Simulations — SIMULTECH 2019

https://arxiv.org/abs/1905.05940. Published as a conference paper and won the best poster award in SIMULTECH 2019. Won the Technion Computer Science department's 2019 excellent project competition.

Beholder-GAN: Generation and Beautification of Facial Images with Conditioning on Their Beauty Level — ICIP 2019

https://arxiv.org/abs/1902.02593. Published as a conference paper in ICIP 2019 and won the best undergraduate project in IMVC 2019.

Affect-based Intrinsic Rewards for Exploration and Learning — In review

https://arxiv.org/abs/1912.00403. Submitted as a conference paper to IROS 2020.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Microsoft Research, WA — Research Intern

2019

Discovering new opportunities using affect-based driven approaches in autonomous driving.

Rafael, Israel — R&D Student

2018 - 2019

Research and design of deep learning algorithms, Implementation of deep learning-based products using dockers.

ClickTale, Israel — IT Corporate Engineer

2014 - 2015

Managing servers, networking and security systems (Cisco and Checkpoint environments), developing software applications for automation.

Military Service, Israel — Networking Team Leader

2011 - 2014

Managing servers and networking environment, developing software applications for automation. CCNA authorization (networking authorization by CISCO). Release as a staff sergeant.

EDUCATION

Technion, Israel — BSc in Computer Science

2015 - 2019 GPA 87.0/100, Dean's list three times.

TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

Experience in ML and computational frameworks – TensorFlow, Pytorch, ONNX, and Caffe.

Python as a preferred programming language.

LANGUAGES

Hebrew – Mother's tongue

English – Excellent